coupondipity.com 2016-10-19

# Privacy Policy & Disclosure

This policy is valid from 01 May 2012

Thank you for following the Official Coupondipity® Blog, which is presented by 

Vicki S. Floyd

We are committed to creating a community that both encourages self-expression and also reflects my values, including respect for the dignity, rights and property of others. We ask all fans to do their part to help us to achieve this goal and not post content that:

*is threatening, abusive, defamatory, obscene, indecent or objectionable  
*is fraudulent, deceptive or misleading;  
*violates any law or regulation; or  
*is otherwise offensive

We will monitor every posting and we reserve the right to remove any content that violates our community guidelines or that we otherwise determine is not appropriate. The content posted by fans and/or followers does not reflect our views or opinions. All content posted must comply with Google.com’s Statement of Rights and Responsibilities and other policies.

In addition to the rights that you grant to google.com, you (and your parent/legal guardian on your behalf if you are a minor in your jurisdiction of residence) grant to Coupondipity® and its affiliates a royalty-free license to use your content in any manner or media, globally, forever, without any obligation to you. This includes the right to use any ideas you submit (including ideas about our products or advertising campaigns) in any manner that we choose, without any obligation to you.

Coupondipity® is intended to be a fun space for you and other fans. Please note that we do not endorse nor take responsibility for the accuracy of information, opinions, claims, or advice shared here by fans. In particular, please be aware that Coupondipity® has not tested any of the consumer tips provided herein for either effectiveness or safety.

If you later change your mind and no longer want to follow Carmen’s Coupondipity®, please feel free to “unfollow” our page by clicking the link “unfollow.” Thank you for visiting Coupondipity®.

* * * * *

This blog is a personal blog written and edited by me. For questions about this blog, please contact Coupondipity® (Vicki at Coupondipity@live.com).

This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post may not always be identified as paid or sponsored content.

The owner(s) of this blog may be compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog may receive compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.

To get your own policy, go to http://www.disclosurepolicy.org

* * * * *

**** PRIVACY POLICY ****

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Coupondipity® collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the Coupondipity® website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Coupondipity®.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

Coupondipity® collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _\- To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature:_ To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * _\- To send periodic emails:_ The email address Users provide will only be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**** PRIZE/GIVEAWAY DISCLAIMER ****

When I offer prizes for giveaways on my blog Coupondipity I do so on good faith that the sponsor will honor our arrangement and send the winner/winners their prize/prizes.

If for some reason you are a prize winner and you do not receive your prize in a reasonable amount of time please contact me directly at coupondipity@live.com. I will contact the sponsor to try and find out about the status of your prize.

**In the event the sponsor does not reply to my e-mails or fails to send the prize I am not to be held responsible or liable in any way. Failure to produce a prize falls solely on the sponsor. I cannot be held accountable for the actions of the sponsor**.

Please note that sometimes prizes take a while to process and ship. Please allow for a reasonable amount of time to receive your prize. If you do not receive anything within 3 weeks please feel free to contact me. Prizes can take from 1-8 weeks to be shipped out, depending on the prize and the company. Please do not wait months to contact me about a prize not received because by then it could be too late.

**All rules of the giveaway must be followed or entries will be voided.  **Failure to comply with the main entry requirement will null and void all extra entries. **   **I have the right to remove entries if I feel they are in violation of any rules (Twitter and Facebook rules included) or considered SPAM. I also check all extra entry options to make sure they are legitimate and follow the rules.

Occasionally a sponsor might have rules set up as to how many wins a single person can have each month. If a sponsor does not want to award multiple prizes to a single winner during a specific time frame I have no control over that and is an issue the winner must take up with the sponsor. Sponsor has the right to refuse awarding prize for duplicate winners from other blogs.

Giveaways are open to U.S residents and occasionally Canadian residents, unless otherwise noted. You must be 18 years or older to enter.

Winners are chosen using Random.org. Winners are contacted via e-mail and have 48 hours to reply or a new winner will be chosen in their place. Please be sure to check your SPAM folder. I am not liable for e-mails that end up in your SPAM folder and are deleted by you.  (Except where otherwise stated in the Terms and Conditions in each Individual Giveaway)

When using the Twitter “tweeting” option you are allowed a maximum of 1 tweet per day. All others will be disqualified.

Entering any giveaways on this site means that you have read and acknowledged all points in this disclaimer.

**Compliance with children’s online privacy protection act**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Coupondipity® has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site,  revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

www.coupondipity.blogspot.com

Jacksonville, FL 32277

coupondipity@live.com
